looneytunesphonics.com 2014-06-20

# Our Privacy Policy : Reading Programs for Kids : Looney Tunes Phonics

## WE NEVER SELL YOUR EMAIL OR OTHER CONTACT INFORMATION TO OTHER COMPANIES, PERIOD!

ClickN KIDS online products are available through its web site on a subscription basis. Use of these subscription services shall constitute your consent to the terms of this privacy policy. We may collect and maintain certain information associated with your subscription. ClickN KIDS online products require registration to access content and manage your account. These accounts are registered by the parent or legal guardian and personally identifiable information, such as email address, phone number, street address, city, state and zip code are required for account registration. We do not require nor request any personally identifiable information about children for registration or usage of ClickN KIDS online products. All school student accounts for ClickN KIDS online products are created by the student's teacher, and are attached to the teacher's account. The student names entered into the program are chosen solely at the discretion of the teacher.

ClickN KIDS adheres to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and the guidelines of the Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. in our web site and in all our registration processes.

## How secure is shopping at ClickN KIDS web site?

We use the industry leader in secure online transactions, Verisign Payment Services, which employs Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt any credit card information you provide to us while placing an order online.

Throughout our web site we may include links to other web sites. Our privacy policy does not apply to these external links. The privacy policy of the third party web site governs the information collection and usage on such third party site.

ClickN KIDS, Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliates ("ClickN KIDS") values and protects your privacy. We thank you for the trust that you place in us and we want you to know that the information you share with us will be treated with care.

**ClickN KIDS** **DOES NOT SELL** "Personally Identifiable Information" ("PII") **collected via this Website or via the e-mails covered by this Online Privacy Statement with entities outside of** **ClickN KIDS** **so that they can independently market their own products and services directly to you.**

The objective of this Online Privacy Statement is to disclose and explain what **PII** and other information we collect, use, and share and to explain the privacy choices that you can make. We encourage you to read this Online Privacy Statement, as well as those of all websites that you visit.

This Online Privacy Statement applies solely to: (1) information collected by ClickN KIDS or our "Vendors" via: (a) www.clicknkids.com and all services and webpages available under those ClickN KIDS websites that display, link to, or incorporate by reference this Online Privacy Statement ("Website"), or (b) e-mail, as described in this Online Privacy Statement; and (2) United States visitors to this Website. 

ClickN KIDS may provide links to third-party websites. This Online Privacy Statement does not apply to any information you may provide while on such sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on those sites before providing any of your PII on such sites.

## Advertisements On This Website and Other Websites

ClickN KIDS may hire Vendors to place advertisements on this Website and other websites, and to perform tracking and reporting functions for this Website and other websites. These Vendors do not collect PII in this process, and we do not give any PII to them as part of this process. This Online Privacy Statement does not cover the collection methods or use of the information collected by these Vendors. These Vendors have their own privacy policies and may be members of the [Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI")](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). To remove yourself from some or all NAI member advertising programs, please visit the [NAI Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and follow the relevant instructions.

## Using Your E-Mail Address

We may use your e-mail address to send the following types of e-mail messages to you:

  * **Updates and Valuable Offers.** We may send you e-mail account updates, offers for our products and services, requests for enrollment, as well as valuable offers from our Business Partners.
  * **Regularly Scheduled E-mail Newsletters** related to ClickN KIDS products or services in which you are enrolled or newsletters that you have elected to receive.
  * **Account Service Information.** We may send you e-mail service notifications that are related to your account(s) or products and services in which you are enrolled. These include e-mails that provide account information, answer your questions about a product or service, facilitate or confirm a sale, or fulfill a legal or regulatory disclosure requirement.
  * **Optional Messages.** You may also choose to receive other types of e-mail messages from us, including additional alerts and notifications beyond those noted above.

## Transfers of Information to Other Countries

Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this Online Privacy Statement may involve the transfer of your PII to various countries around the world. By submitting your PII to ClickN KIDS via this Website or in response to our e-mails, you consent to such transfers and to the processing of this information in various countries around the world.

## Children's Privacy

This Website is intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly solicit data online from, or market online to, children under the age of 13. If we knowingly obtain PII in error on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems. ClickN KIDS adheres to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and the guidelines of the Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. in our web site and in all our registration processes.  
ClickN KIDS online products require registration to access content and manage your account. These accounts are registered by the parent or legal guardian and personally identifiable information, such as email address, phone number, street address, city, state and zip code are required for account registration. We do not require nor request any personally identifiable information about children for registration or usage of ClickN KIDS online products. All school student accounts for ClickN KIDS online products are created by the student's teacher, and are attached to the teacher's account. The student names entered into the program are chosen solely at the discretion of the teacher.

## The Information We Collect

When you visit this Website, we or our Vendors collect information, including PII, that you provide, such as during your registration as a user or your application for a product or service. When browsing this Website, you may choose not to provide us with any PII, such as by not registering.

We automatically collect your "IP Address" used to connect your computer to the Internet, browser type and version, operating system, and computer platform. We or our Vendors also use "Cookies" or similar technologies, sometimes in combination with "Web Beacons," to collect some statistical data when you receive our e-mails or browse this Website, such as e-mail response rates, average time spent on this Website, pages viewed, information searched for, access times, "Clickstream Data," and other relevant information about your online experience. Cookies and Web Beacons set by ClickN KIDS or by our Vendors do not capture any PII.  
Cookies are widely used, and most web browsers are configured initially to accept Cookies automatically. If you prefer not to accept Cookies, you may adjust your browser settings to notify you when a Cookie is about to be sent, or you may configure your browser to refuse Cookies automatically. However, if you turn off Cookies, or refuse to accept a request to place a Cookie, some features and services on this Website may not function properly and the advertising you receive when you visit this Website may not be as relevant to you or tailored to your interests.

## How We Use and Share The Information We Collect

ClickN KIDS uses the information we or our Vendors collect about and from you, including PII, your computer's IP Address, and information collected and/or stored in a Cookie or similar technology, to personalize our communications with you and provide you with a more effective user experience (e.g., to recognize you when you return to this Website, save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts); complete your transactions; respond to your requests; deliver the products and services in which you enroll, request, or for which you apply; and notify you of account or product/service updates. We or our Vendors may also use Cookies, Web Beacons, or similar technologies to present you with tailored offers on this Website or other websites on which ClickN KIDS advertises, or in our e-mails, and to analyze the effectiveness of such offers. ClickN KIDS may also use the information that we or our Vendors collect from or about you online to market to you through alternative channels, including offline means. To assist us with the uses described in this Online Privacy Statement, if you choose to furnish us with PII or if we have personal or other information about you from publicly available or other sources, this information may be linked to the information that we or our Vendors have collected online, including information stored in a Cookie. However, if you have deleted and disabled Cookies, we will not be able to link Cookie information with the account(s) you may have with ClickN KIDS.

**ClickN KIDS** **DOES NOT SELL** **PII** **collected via this Website or via the e-mails covered by this Online Privacy Statement with entities outside of** **ClickN KIDS** **so that they can independently market their own products and services directly to you.** ClickN KIDS may share your information within our ClickN KIDS family of companies as required or permitted by law. To provide products and services to you, we may also share your information with carefully selected Vendors and "Business Partners" with whom we work. This includes companies that manage accounts; offer affinity, frequent-user, and reward programs; companies that perform marketing services and other business operations for us; and companies whose products or services are provided as a benefit of your account with us. All companies that act on our behalf are required to safeguard PII.

If you apply for products and services online, we may share information we collect from or about you with credit bureaus and similar organizations if we have your consent or when required or permitted by law. We may also use or disclose your information, including PII, to comply with the law or in response to a subpoena, court order, government request, or other legal process, or as otherwise permitted by law; to perform charge verifications; to report or collect debts owed; to reduce fraud or criminal activity; to protect the legal rights of ClickN KIDS, our customers, this Website, or the users of this Website; to allow a purchaser of an ClickN KIDS product, to continue using your information to serve you; or as otherwise permitted by this Online Privacy Statement.

## Your Communication and Privacy Choices

ClickN KIDS respects the choices that you make regarding your privacy. You may request that we no longer send you direct marketing e-mails and/or offline offers or promotions. Please note that it may take some time, consistent with applicable law, for us to process your request. 

  * If you are an ClickN KIDS registered user and you do not want to receive future offers or promotions from ClickN KIDS about our products and services, or the products and services of our Business Partners, or, if you do not want to receive future offers or promotions other than e-mail offers or promotions, please call 1-866-876-0419. In addition, if you have received certain marketing e-mails from ClickN KIDS but you no longer want to receive them, you may also follow the unsubscribe instructions that are located at the bottom of those e-mail messages.

If you have multiple accounts with us, you will need to express your privacy choices for each of them separately using the applicable procedures above. Please note that even if you choose not to receive future direct marketing e-mails and/or offline offers or promotions, we may continue to send you service notifications, via e-mails or offline means, about your account(s) and related products and services, and such notifications may still include offers or promotions about your account(s) and related products and services. Such notifications may also provide account information (including information about servicing communications based on your customer status), answer your questions about a product or service, facilitate or confirm a sale, or fulfill a legal or regulatory requirement. In addition, you may still continue to receive marketing e-mails and offline offers or promotions from ClickN KIDS. 

## Securing Your Information

We use reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect your PII from unauthorized access and use. Do not use e-mail to send us any PII, since it would be unencrypted and can be read by anyone who receives or intercepts it. 

## Updating Your Information

If you wish to correct or update the PII related to your online ClickN KIDS account(s), please use your User ID and Password to log in to our home page. You will then have access to your PII and can correct or update it. 

## Contacting ClickN KIDS  

If you are a ClickN KIDS subscriber and have questions about this Online Privacy Statement, please call Customer Service at 1-877-CLICK ABC. 

## Changes to This Online Privacy Statement

ClickN KIDS reserves the right to change this Online Privacy Statement at any time by posting revisions on this Website. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

## Glossary of Key Terms

**Business Partner -** A Business Partner is any third party with which ClickN KIDS conducts business, except that the term Business Partner does not include a Vendor, as defined below.   
**Clickstream Data -** Clickstream Data is information that users generate as they move from page to page and click on items within a website, usually stored in log files. Website designers can use Clickstream Data to improve users' experiences with a website.   
**Cookie -** A Cookie is a small piece of information that a website transfers to the hard drive of a visitor's computer for record-keeping purposes. Cookies provide visitors a personalized experience on this Website by enabling us to determine unique preferences and trends based on visits to this Website and to other websites.   
**IP Address -** An IP Address is a number that is assigned to your computer automatically and required for using the Internet.   
**Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") -** PII is information collected online by ClickN KIDS or by our Vendors that identifies the person to whom such information pertains, including without limitation name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address.   
**Vendor(s) -** A Vendor is any third party that performs business operations on behalf of ClickN KIDS, including without limitation printing, mailing services and other communications services (e.g., e-mail, direct mail, or otherwise), marketing, data processing, customer acquisition and servicing, collections, or advertisement management.   
**Web Beacon -** A Web Beacon, also known as a "clear GIF" (a common format for image files), is an invisible file located on webpages that you visit. They are often used in combination with a Cookie to track navigation of a site. If you visit a page on this Website that contains a Web Beacon, it communicates with your computer to determine, among other things, whether you have been to that page before or viewed a particular advertisement.
